Contact

tatiana@panteleeva.it

www.linkedin.com/in/panteleeva (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

TensorFlow

CCNA

CCNA Security

Languages

French (Elementary)

Swedish (Professional Working)

Russian (Native or Bilingual)

English (Full Professional)

Certifications

Cisco Certified Specialist - Enterprise Core

Cisco Certified Specialist -Enterprise Advanced Infrastructure Implementation

Cisco DevNet Associate Fundamentals Course

Machine Learning in Production

Cisco Certified Network Professional Enterprise (CCNP Enterprise)

Tatiana Panteleeva

Al Engineer

Stockholm, Stockholm County, Sweden

Summary

I've got a Master's Degree in Math and Computer Science and have worked for more than 10 years in the IT area as a network engineer. I'm confident with Python and Git. The areas of my interest are Generative AI/LLM and LLMOps and I'm constantly learning. I'm also working with:

- Langchain
- PyTorch, TensorFlow
- HuggingFace platform
- Anyscale

Experience

Freelance

Al Enthusiast

October 2023 - Present (1 year 8 months)

I'm most interested in LLM and AI development. I'm doing some experiments with frontier and open-sourced models, including implementing RAG and AI Agents.

Chernogolovka

Network Engineer

July 2021 - July 2023 (2 years 1 month)

Configured network devices Cisco, Huawei for distributed corporate network. Worked as a solo network architect for network modernization project and as a part of a team for troubleshooting network problems. I designed and implemented documentation and monitoring systems and also wrote scripts for remote configuration network devices.

Convey Plus, Telecommunications Network Engineer April 2010 - May 2020 (10 years 2 months) Maintained Cisco routers, switches configurations, monitored and documented network devices. The project I worked the most was to optimize LAN using performance reports and monitoring applications in 24/7 environment.

Gazinformservice

Network Engineer

September 2008 - April 2010 (1 year 8 months)

Managed Cisco routers, switches, firewalls. Supervised alignment and maintenance of test equipment, operations and preventive maintenance. Member of the systems compatibility test team responsible for verifying the functionality of various vendors' equipment with existing infrastructure.

A-real Consulting, System Integrator

Network Engineer

November 2007 - September 2008 (11 months)

Designed and implemented local area networks for multiple customers.

Evaluated customer needs and proposed solutions for those needs. Assisted in management of various contract customer networks.

Education

Yaroslavl Demidov State University

Master's degree, Mathematics and Computer Science (2002 - 2008)